we're trying this again we're going live
I am going to fill the questions
[Music]
now
and then we should write in
functionalities where the car is driving
so similar to what the peyote and so
right now the device that you see and
this is what right now the only devices
possible pilot but we are very opened
and like more and more devices that
actually could support the support of a
part which is one main reason why we
move the pilot of this sort so that
people can actually port it they're
aware
we have any plans to use that or did you
actually use any simulation when you do
that with payment system or is it all on
life days we might know we do we do is
already simulator so we do use
simulators to plan regression tests to
develop our features it was like we have
to use simulators so my cartoon again we
extensively use simulators but the
interesting simulators that we are
building is the simulator that we hope
is gonna allow us a flying personal
learning to try this is kind of a
different simulator that requires us
having like a very good understanding of
the surrounding and then creating a
system where the car can be
automatically rewarded if he drives well
and being like the same honest when he
doesn't drive well automatically
understanding how to drive this is like
one of the research projects that we are
working on which allows us to add like
other models more scaling and having
more leverage of the data that we have
without having to work all the features
for planning so it's some sort of like
how do we copy apply machine learning to
the block if it does like the planning
of the Sodra here and so this is what
like simulated everything
can you select the particle of
communication in SoCal's like a
different light it's use the way that
these issues communicate with each other
is true and is a and protocol which is
they are coming up communication area
network I mean my hand itself is off the
network like you can't like any as I can
as can portable communication seems like
many years it's actually mandatory to
use to your scanner since I think the
eight is so now I mean you have to have
physical access to the car in order to
have like any sort of like issues like
issues like devices that are connected
on internet and yes you have to be you
have to make sure that you cannot ever
you are going to have a tax through the
internet connectivity of your device yes
our device is interconnected and that's
how we yeah you know the same thing
basically that like the same processes
but like many many many many cars like
software software like on the same
problem as before we're gonna see more
and more cars having capability of being
like updated over yeah right this is the
kind of thing that we believe it's
absolutely so it's kind of like we
believe is like super strange they're
like $30,000 object that you buy today
cannot be updated over yeah like if you
need a software update and regarding
like safety yes I mean of course it's
our concern right but like how many cars
have been act in the last like how many
classic you or they have been hacked and
they made some damage because they be
not
I had heard about about one so it is a
concern clarify what she said earlier
about reading the censors so if there
whatever sensor suite is in place for a
task that comes are you're able to use
those sensors and incorporated into
quick and then towards the answer you
were saying about items that are
available for purchase you mentioned
something about if you wanted to know
more about positioning of your vehicle
what how precise is what is it
so do you some lousy oh so it's like so
this is like you blocks I'm not sure if
you are familiar with this use like a
new blocks processing antenna
wherever you have access actually to all
GPS and so thought about like how much
post processing you do about it and you
can get like very precise that you can
actually like you use the correct like
post processing and so in this regard
okay this is like a little spoiler but
this week we're gonna release idea here
so this week we're kind of like there's
an engineer like our health organization
who is actually going to going to make
an open source of post processor or GPS
data and get like the best across it is
you can get the type of response team I
mean like so no micro GPS as opposed to
regular
the difference Thank You procedure yeah
well so we do the post-processing not
assuming that you do like any vision
feature magic which allows you to be
even way more precise so just by GPS
a-gps processing and some sort of light
filter like you're playing a Kalman
filter and you're like sense of a like
accelerometer you can get between like
helping me there procedure well you
would be able to localize all but if you
have the map that you can centimeter
across because once you know which lane
you are into then you just have to find
like some visual feature like line lines
and localize yourself within very are
totally within centimeter within the
lane lines so yes I mean this is not
assuming any visual organization if you
want to use visualization then you can
get like centimeter accurate because for
example I necessarily you know which
lane which lane you are into you see
where the lane lane lines are and then
you just localized yourself relatively
to the main lines for which you
perfectly know the position because they
are on your high-definition maps and
then you can organize yourself at least
in one dimension which is dimension that
matters within like Yousaf meter how
much is it obviously like subtyping to
me that I really like
[Music]
but I'm funny that I'll commute that we
post-processing yes we're gonna lose the
tools do I should achieve that and this
is all every all the software that goes
into a source yes
oops sorry we have our Canadian crew
that's downstairs so maybe I'll have a
tour
film you guys while I go get that
Canadians oh sorry to interrupt
yeah he's talking there's there's 24
people Greg can you do me a great big
favor can you hold them until I'm back
I'm just gonna run to get the Canadians
you know
[Music]
I think stay the hardware yeah any
thought that might be enough but if it's
not they're gonna replace the hardware
is that still kind of industry
with sooner the thing is something today
whether it's writing applications when
the machine learns it creates a solution
you are you are yeah
[Music]
yeah
I studied like many engineering
I was busy - yelling at bachelor and
then I switched to automotive mechanical
engineers for master I moved to United
States I need some work in the vehicle
so I moved to Tesla Tesla for about like
five six years and the pilot then I
joined I met George which there is the
founder combi and I got very excited
about the project and I'm still happy so
I'm very excited about like the idea of
like solving practical problems like SCU
job I get excited about problems where
is it a huge opportunity of like making
things better and I just see like a huge
proportion of like investment other
sources like overnight level 4 I just
feel like okay well let's picture like
let me chew Stephanie like over a loop
and so I'm excited about solving
problems divide like positive actually
impact on people's life
I understand thing there's issues of
propriety this about people's are so
currently and replace any money
OS in most us jurisdictions in the world
you invalidate warranty do you have
plans to so obviously I said before like
our our plan is to work with it is to
work with humans player we have to work
together like in order to make apparel
successful we need to ship it like we
need to work together to yes and so yeah
this is the plan like the plan is like
it's not in part in anything like the
work with aftermarket product it's
actually working working with them and
working together like exchanging
information about like how there are the
interface of the cap works and making it
compatible like what I'm saying
compatible at the point like they do
with the polar project they're trying to
do the same thing I think like their
approach is the totally different from
us we try to make it working on tasks
that people own which is why like we
want to make it accessible right we want
to make like open pilots something that
people can access and so we to like
definitely try to achieve our end goal
but the way that we're doing is very
different like we try to make it open
pilot working on to the ACE car there
try to make a map I like they are polar
projects working on we with cars that
cost more than $1,000 and just research
projects and so they're like and it only
works on like very heavy computers like
we use by consumer we use things that
you can find in focus liking the smart
phones you can buy today is they argue
that is sufficient to run a pilot so the
direction is very different we try to
value like accessibility
and orally like transparency and early
adoptability of the features while while
I think Apple is taking more like and
testifying like something that means
like very heavy they basically didn't
consider like any constraints in term of
like a car accessibility and so the part
to get there is different we have seven
million miles we plan 12 like people
live in a year they said like more than
100 ma and 100 medium eyes I don't think
like the polar project is ever gonna get
close to that like Apple is now gonna be
able to define their own HD maps on
different the day today their devices
collect because the amount of people
using their devices is it's possible
it's possible but like I mean okay so
which which which hardware do they need
that do they need like they need like
lighter so do they need which I mean
like I have not seen like a car driving
with the poor law and having like
satisfactory level to system so like
I've seen like they most of their
expensive cars with gliders coming
Estrada so Atlanta car probably driving
at the polar but like it doesn't seem
like they are on a part of ship ability
in terms of like are they on a part of
like shipping their product anytime so
they are they ready to ship it anytime
soon so we try to behave in that sense
by developing it on cars and
hardware that can be found today's today
development cycle automobile if it sees
five years for to build into a car etc
and you're talking about level two and
hopefully level four will have taken off
and completes at least in some parts of
the world then what is this selling
point so if I'm in Tier one or I'm an
OEM what are you going to tell me that
is going to make me say yesterday yeah
so before they said that it's not gonna
make like mockingly majority of people's
life that they're it's only gonna work
like in very limited environment it's
not proven to work yet I know like way
manaus that they ship this month like
they are their first like project
program community like a tire behind
behind the wheel economy works we very
climate where they're like in Arizona
I'm not like I don't think like a level
four he's gonna he's gonna anti
ownership this is like the main point
like people are still gonna buy cars for
many many years like decades from now
so the problem like we are not competing
with wait wait we are not competing with
with this idea of like creating data for
system I actually oh but they succeed
I'm not so sure they gonna make people's
life better because like partly san
francisc is like traffic is traffic is
the main proper right and so making
transportation cheaper in cars does it
make talking better now for is gonna
make it worse like it's probably gonna
make like way more working some assist
people and me is probably gonna make
like our commute board it's coming the
public cheaper third wars like it's
gonna spend more time job so
I am saying the comet doesn't try to
make commuting cities cheaper he's gonna
try to make it better but not cheap
he's not trying to make your commute on
highway definitely better today I just I
just think like trying to solve like
think that is trying to solve we could
be solved in different ways maybe better
public transportation like we already
have what we need
not so sure it's gonna solve practical
problems but I'm excited about the
project I'm excited about like detecting
a challenge it seems like a body project
- let's stop there so people can get
some food and engineers are here we have
a we have a shop we have a mobile shop
with us so if you want to get tour
t-shirts if you want to get Aeons if you
want to get your a Spanos whatever Nick
will be working that back there or
wherever Nick outside yeah help your
guys to pizza and thank you so much for
coming like I said people will be here
to continue answering your questions and
yeah
thank you guys all right bye scobie's